Tufts University School of Medicine Yearbook UP150
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts University School of Medicine Yearbook
1924 -- 2020
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Medicine
UP150
0.25 Linear Feet
80 Volumes
5757 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains annual yearbooks of the School of Medicine starting in 1924, with the exception of the 1940s. It was originally called Caduceus. No yearbook was published for the Class of 1970.
Biographical / Historical
The Tufts University School of Medicine was voted into existence by the Trustees on April 22, 1893. It was formed by the secession of seven faculty from the College of Physicians and Surgeons in Boston, a school which was formed in 1880. These "original seven" faculty members successfully lobbied to establish a medical school under the auspices of Tufts College.
The "original seven" first faculty of the Medical School were William Chipman, Henry W. Dudley, Walter L. Hall, John W. Johnson, Albert Nott, Charles P. Thayer, and Frank Wheatley. All had been members of the College of Physicians and Surgeons, but had been dissatisfied with the operations of that institution since it opened in 1880.They believed that in order to raise the standards of the school and provide for the necessary laboratory and clinical work, the school should affiliate with a college or university. President Capen was sympathetic to the idea of Tufts expanding into the realm of medical education, leading the group to concentrate their efforts on affiliation with Tufts.
The new school, which was designated the Medical School of Tufts College, opened its doors in October 1893 with a student body of eighty students. The school was, from the very beginning, coeducational, and of the twenty-two students who graduated that first year, eight were women.
The Medical School was initially located on three floors of a building at 188 Boylston Street in Boston, now the site of the Four Seasons Hotel. The building, which had formerly served as the home of the College of Physicians and Surgeons, was owned by Tufts as an investment property, and was taken for use of the Medical School upon its formation. As enrollment increased rapidly in the first years of the school's operation, the school acquired additional facilities for use in the area. By 1897 the school's growth forced it to seek a new facility. A renovated Baptist church on Shawmut Avenue became the school's new home, but the establishment of the Dental School in 1899 meant that another move was necessary. This time a building was constructed to house both schools on Huntington Avenue, which served as the Medical School's home until 1949, when it moved to its current location on Harrison Avenue in downtown Boston.
By 1905, the Medical School was the largest such school in New England, with a faculty of 105 and 403 students. While enrollments continued to climb, growth of the school was hindered by the lack of any substantial endowment and the failure to obtain a hospital for exclusive use of the school's clinical training needs.
In the first decades of the Medical School's existence there was ongoing concern about admission requirements and the implications these held for the quality of medical education and graduates of the program. Initially, a high school degree from an approved school, or examination in high school subjects was required for admission. Many felt this to be too lax, but others were hesitant to require a full college degree for admission, believing that this would put an unnecessary financial and time burden on students. However, as the American Medical Association criteria for ranking medical schools continued to be revised, admissions standards were gradually increased to a bachelor's degree by the 1932-33 academic year.
In 1929 an alliance was formed between Boston Dispensary, the Floating Hospital for Infants and Children, and the medical and dental schools, constituting the basis for the formation of the New England Medical Center (NEMC) in 1930.This served as the impetus for the medical and dental schools to move from the Huntington Avenue location to downtown Boston. However, before this could take place it was necessary to raise funds to construct a new facility, a task which was made all the more challenging in that it was undertaken in the depression years of the 1930s.
During World War II, the Medical School went on a full-year, accelerated academic calendar to meet the increased wartime demand for medical personnel. Plans continued to go ahead for construction of a new facility downtown, and the move was accomplished in 1949.This move signified the realization of the school's long-term goal of providing close affiliation with a hospital facility for its students.
Expanding curricular programs and departments to keep apace with the growing medical field placed ongoing strains on the finances of the Medical School. With the majority of income being generated by tuition revenues, efforts were intensified starting in the 1950s to seek additional public and private grant funding for projects and to drastically increase the school's endowment. Faculty were successful in obtaining funding from sources such as the Ford Foundation, the National Public Health Service, and the National Cancer Institute. In 1975-76, Professor William B. Schwartz, chair of the Department of Medicine, became the first holder of the Vannevar Bush University Professorship, the first endowed professorship in the university's history.
For much of its history, the Medical School has drawn its student body largely from the New England states. Since the 1950s this has gradually changed, with slightly less than half of entering students in 1999 coming from the six New England states.
- School of Medicine Yearbook, 1924 -- 2020; UP150.001; 0.25 Linear Feet; 80 Volumes; 5757 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains yearbooks for the Tufts University School of Medicine called the Caduceus.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Caduceus (Medical College Yearbook), 1924; UP150.001.001 (Volume 1)
    book
  - Caduceus (Medical College Yearbook), 1925; UP150.001.002 (Volume 2)
  - Caduceus (Medical College Yearbook), 1926; UP150.001.003 (Volume 3)
  - The 1927 Caduceus [yearbook], UP150.001.004.00001 (Volume 4)
    Yearbook for the Tufts College Medical School, Class of 1927.
    School yearbooks; Students; School of Medicine; Tufts College
  - Caduceus (Medical College Yearbook), 1928; UP150.001.005 (Volume 5)
  - Caduceus (Medical College Yearbook), 1929; UP150.001.006 (Volume 6)
  - Caduceus (Medical College Yearbook), 1930; UP150.001.007 (Volume 7)
  - Caduceus (Medical College Yearbook), 1931; UP150.001.008 (Volume 8)
  - 1932 Caduceus [yearbook], UP150.001.009.00001 (Volume 9)
    Yearbook for the Tufts College Medical School, Class of 1932.
    Students; School yearbooks; Tufts College; School of Medicine
  - Caduceus (Medical College Yearbook), 1933; UP150.001.010 (Volume 10)
  - Caduceus (Medical College Yearbook), 1934; UP150.001.011.00001 (Box 11)
  - Seminar (Medical Yearbook), 1951; UP150.001.011.00002 (Box 11)
  - Medical Yearbook, 1952; UP150.001.011.00003 (Box 11)
  - Tufts Medical '52 [yearbook], 1952; UP150.001.012.00001 (Volume 12)
    Yearbook for the Tufts College Medical School, Class of 1952.
  - Tufts Medical '53 [yearbook], 1953; UP150.001.013.00001 (Volume 13)
    Yearbook for the Tufts College Medical School, Class of 1953.
  - Tufts College Medical School [yearbook], 1954; UP150.001.014.00001 (Volume 14)
    Yearbook for the Tufts College Medical School, Class of 1954
  - Tufts University School of Medicine [yearbook], 1955; UP150.001.015.00001 (Volume 15)
    Yearbook for the Tufts University School of Medicine, Class of 1955.
    School yearbooks; Students; School of Medicine; Tufts University
  - Tufts University School of Medicine [yearbook], 1956; UP150.001.016.00001 (Volume 16)
    Yearbook for the Tufts University School of Medicine, Class of 1956.
    Students; School yearbooks; School of Medicine; Tufts University
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 7, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00009 (Volume 16)
      From the School of Medicine yearbook, 1956
      image/tiff
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 8, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00010 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 9, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00011 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 10, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00012 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 11, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00013 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 12, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00014 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 13, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00015 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 14, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00016 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 15, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00017 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 16, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00018 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 17, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00019 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 18, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00020 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 19, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00021 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 20, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00022 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 21, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00023 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 22, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00024 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 23, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00025 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 24, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00026 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 25, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00027 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 26, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00028 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 27, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00029 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 28, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00030 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 29, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00031 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 30, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00032 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 31, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00033 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 32, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00034 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 33, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00035 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 34, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00036 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 35, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00037 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 36, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00038 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 37, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00039 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 38, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00040 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 39, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00041 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 40, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00042 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 41, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00043 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 42, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00044 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 43, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00045 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 44, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00046 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 45, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00047 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 46, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00048 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 47, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00049 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 48, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00050 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 49, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00051 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 50, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00052 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 51, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00053 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 52, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00054 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 53, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00055 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 54, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00056 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 55, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00057 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 56, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00058 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 57, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00059 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 58, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00060 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 59, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00061 (Volume 16)
    - Tufts University School of Medicine, page 60, 1956; UP150.001.016.00001.00062 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Medical '57 [yearbook], 1957; UP150.001.017.00001 (Volume 17)
    Yearbook for the Tufts University Medical School, Class of 1957.
    Students; School yearbooks; Tufts University; School of Medicine
    - Tufts Medical '57, cover, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00001 (Volume 17)
      From the Medical School yearbook, 1957
    - Tufts Medical '57, inside cover, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00002 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, dedication, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00003 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 1, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00004 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 2, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00005 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 3, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00006 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 4, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00007 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 5, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00008 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 6, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00009 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 7, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00010 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 8, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00011 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 9, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00012 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 10, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00013 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 11, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00014 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 12, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00015 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 13, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00016 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 14, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00017 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 15, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00018 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 16, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00019 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 17, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00020 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 18, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00021 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 19, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00022 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 20, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00023 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 21, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00024 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 22, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00025 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 23, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00026 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 24, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00027 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 25, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00028 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 26, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00029 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 27, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00030 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 28, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00031 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 29, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00032 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 30, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00033 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 31, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00034 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 32, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00035 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 33, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00036 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 34, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00037 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 35, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00038 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 36, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00039 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 37, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00040 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 38, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00041 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 39, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00042 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 40, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00043 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 41, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00044 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 42, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00045 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 43, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00046 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 44, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00047 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 45, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00048 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 46, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00049 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 47, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00050 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 48, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00051 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 49, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00052 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 50, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00053 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 51, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00054 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 52, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00055 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 53, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00056 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 54, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00057 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 55, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00058 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 56, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00059 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 57, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00060 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 58, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00061 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, page 59, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00062 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, inside back cover, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00063 (Volume 17)
    - Tufts Medical '57, back cover, 1957; UP150.001.017.00001.00064 (Volume 17)
  - Caduceus 1958 [yearbook], UP150.001.018.00001 (Volume 18)
    Yearbook for the Tufts University School of Medicine, Class of 1958.
    - Caduceus 1958, cover, UP150.001.018.00001.00001 (Volume 18)
      From the School of Medicine yearbook, 1958
    - Caduceus 1958, inside cover, UP150.001.018.00001.00002 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 1, UP150.001.018.00001.00003 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 2, UP150.001.018.00001.00004 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 3, UP150.001.018.00001.00005 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 4, UP150.001.018.00001.00006 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 5, UP150.001.018.00001.00007 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 6, UP150.001.018.00001.00008 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 7, UP150.001.018.00001.00009 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 8, UP150.001.018.00001.00010 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 9, UP150.001.018.00001.00011 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 10, UP150.001.018.00001.00012 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 11, UP150.001.018.00001.00013 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 12, UP150.001.018.00001.00014 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 13, UP150.001.018.00001.00015 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 14, UP150.001.018.00001.00016 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 15, UP150.001.018.00001.00017 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 16, UP150.001.018.00001.00018 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 17, UP150.001.018.00001.00019 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 18, UP150.001.018.00001.00020 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 19, UP150.001.018.00001.00021 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 20, UP150.001.018.00001.00022 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 21, UP150.001.018.00001.00023 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 22, UP150.001.018.00001.00024 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 23, UP150.001.018.00001.00025 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 24, UP150.001.018.00001.00026 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 25, UP150.001.018.00001.00027 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 26, UP150.001.018.00001.00028 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 27, UP150.001.018.00001.00029 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 28, UP150.001.018.00001.00030 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 29, UP150.001.018.00001.00031 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 30, UP150.001.018.00001.00032 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 31, UP150.001.018.00001.00033 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 32, UP150.001.018.00001.00034 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 33, UP150.001.018.00001.00035 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 34, UP150.001.018.00001.00036 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 35, UP150.001.018.00001.00037 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 36, UP150.001.018.00001.00038 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 37, UP150.001.018.00001.00039 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 38, UP150.001.018.00001.00040 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 39, UP150.001.018.00001.00041 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 40, UP150.001.018.00001.00042 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 41, UP150.001.018.00001.00043 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 42, UP150.001.018.00001.00044 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 43, UP150.001.018.00001.00045 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 44, UP150.001.018.00001.00046 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 45, UP150.001.018.00001.00047 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 46, UP150.001.018.00001.00048 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 47, UP150.001.018.00001.00049 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 48, UP150.001.018.00001.00050 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 49, UP150.001.018.00001.00051 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 50, UP150.001.018.00001.00052 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 51, UP150.001.018.00001.00053 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 52, UP150.001.018.00001.00054 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 53, UP150.001.018.00001.00055 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 54, UP150.001.018.00001.00056 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 55, UP150.001.018.00001.00057 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 56, UP150.001.018.00001.00058 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 57, UP150.001.018.00001.00059 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 58, UP150.001.018.00001.00060 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 59, UP150.001.018.00001.00061 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 60, UP150.001.018.00001.00062 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 61, UP150.001.018.00001.00063 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 62, UP150.001.018.00001.00064 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 63, UP150.001.018.00001.00065 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, page 64, UP150.001.018.00001.00066 (Volume 18)
    - Caduceus 1958, back cover, UP150.001.018.00001.00067 (Volume 18)
  - Caduceus 1959 [yearbook], UP150.001.019.00001 (Volume 19)
    Yearbook for the Tufts University School of Medicine, Class of 1959.
    - Caduceus 1959, front cover, UP150.001.019.00001.00001 (Volume 19)
      From the School of Medicine yearbook, 1959
    - Caduceus 1959, page 1, UP150.001.019.00001.00002 (Volume 19)
    - Caduceus 1959, page 2, UP150.001.019.00001.00003 (Volume 19)
    - Caduceus 1959, page 3, UP150.001.019.00001.00004 (Volume 19)